THE JUDGE RETURNS
SAMDOORI BARBECUE
ON HOLIDAY FROM SEPT 23 TO OCT 3
EPISODE 13
You'd better clean up properly, okay?
- Bring the keys...
- I'll bring the keys
to your restaurant tomorrow morning.
You've told me a million times.
The judge really only rubs elbows
with the big shots, doesn't he?
Can't believe I made him do dishes.
It's okay, he's my friend.
Leave the place spotless, okay?
Or I'll be too ashamed to see Ae-ja again.
I'm scared of Ms. Ae-ja, too, okay?
- Bye!
- Don't forget the keys!
All thanks to you
the attack dog of the National Assembly is
now the nation's favorite pet.
Everyone gives me
the sweetest smiles these days.
It's so sweet, really.
Quite a lot of market vendor owners
donate their money
to Seonjin Happiness Foundation.
With each small, but meaningful donation
they make
they hope to contribute
to the tuition fees of those in need
and cover the medical bills
of rare disease patients.
That was why I attacked Gwang-to.
Thanks to that, I gained popularity
and I'll likely be nominated by my party
in the next election.
I'll pay for the food tonight.
Let's call it even
with that.
Wow, I didn't realize
I was sitting on a gold mine.
Convince these members of the Assembly
with no chances of getting nominated
and propose a Special Counsel Act
for the former president.
Didn't you say you'd rip him open
and that all I needed to do was
leave a scar?
That's what the money is for.
This is a billion won.
Use it as your campaigning funds.
And that's for your friends
in the Assembly.
Everyone has been so sweet to me lately.
Surprisingly
that makes me not want to take
all this money.
I'm off.
The lease deposit for your house is
500 million won, correct?
And
you'll still say no to two billion won?
The average Korean has
less than 500 million won in assets.
I've been doing my best
to stay average as a politician
but my wife is too savvy, you know?
What would you have done
had I taken the bribe?
I would've understood you.
Not disappointed?
I'm not asking you to push
the Special Counsel Act
to do anything bad for society.
But if they strike back,
I won't get nominated.
I don't want that.
Who do you think will be
Gwang-to's first target
once he's released?
It looks like I've put a leash on myself.
It's okay if your proposal fails.
Just get people worked up
to keep Mr. Park on his toes.
The prosecution will form
a special team for Mr. President
before the opposition proposes
a Special Counsel Act.
It's a shield, in a sense.
Any prosecutor you'd recommend?
I don't have any recommendations
but once the special team sends the list
I'll analyze it and report to you.
There may be some on the list
who may go against your plan.
And you?
Prosecutor Park Cheol-woo would do well.
No.
He's the one who caused all this.
And why?
Cheol-woo only looks ahead.
As long as he has a reason
he'll do everything you want.
He might not understand you
and go overboard
with striking Mr. President.
No.
What Sin-jin really wants is
to get rid of Gwang-to for good.
Arresting all bad guys, no matter what.
That's what justice is to me.
It wouldn't look so good
for the team to be
without the one who started it all.
- Mr. Kang.
- Don't worry.
We'll just get rid of him
if he causes trouble.
If Cheol-woo causes any issues
you'll have to take the responsibility.
It'll be fine.
As it should be.
HERE'S THE REQUESTED INFORMATION
SENIOR PRESIDING JUDGE KIM JIN-HAN
Didn't know
Judge Lee was here.
But who's this guy?
What happened
with Tae-seong?
You have no idea who got in the way?
Well...
I ran into a big guy on my way down
after I thought I'd killed Tae-seong.
A big guy...
How's Mr. Gwak Sun-won?
So, you have no idea
when he'll wake up.
Okay, then.
Get out.
- Ma'am!
- Just go!
If you write about any rumors
about the green belt
I'll sue you!
- Leave me alone.
- Ma'am!
Wait! Just give me a minute to explain.
Did someone named Jang Myeong-ja
buy a plot of land?
Who? Jang?
What are you talking about?
It's all on the Real Estate Statistics
and Transactions Report.
Look at it.
Someone named Jang Myeong-ja bought land.
Whatever.
A man brought all the documents.
Exactly.
Excuse me, then.
Hey, Mr. Lee. It's me.
This looks delicious.
Thank you.
Ms. Jang Myeong-ja works
as a cleaning lady
at Suojae.
Guess where I saw her name.
It must be
one of Gwang-to's shell accounts.
Oh, my.
Guess what the account was used for, then.
If it was recent
it must've been used to buy land
in Hanyang's green belt zone.
No way.
I guess you visited Hanyang recently?
I didn't need to go there to know this.
You have the hunch of a detective.
So, you'll write about it?
Wait! You can't eat it like that.
You have to dip it in this
and swirl it around.
Here. Try it now.
It's good, right?
Darn it.
There's no way I can write about this
for Daejin Daily.
As soon as I mention Seonjin
it won't make it
out of the office.
But you know
there are
over 10,000 internet news outlets
in Korea.
I'll choose one of them, and...
Do you admit to having hidden
500 billion won in slush funds
at Jeongdaun Savings?
You don't need to answer him.
I hear Ms. Kim is
now in Hyenam.
I doubt that she'll get to return.
So, what's your name?
HYENAM DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Man, that's a lot.
This is a case of serial theft
at Ms. Kim Mal-sun's cabbage patch
in Baekbang-ri.
Serial theft at a cabbage patch?
Yeah.
No less than 17 heads of cabbage
disappeared in the past three weeks.
The whole village is worried.
There aren't any surveillance cameras
so it'll likely end up an unresolved case.
What about this?
That's also from Baekbang-ri.
It's a case of an assault on Kkamang
the village chief's breeding goat.
The breeding goat?
Yeah, we have breeding chickens for chicks
and breeding goats for baby goats.
Baekgoo, Mr. Choi's dog
who lives next door to the village chief
bit Kkamang's butt
but they couldn't reach a settlement deal
so the village chief sued Mr. Choi
for property damage.
Where do you even get all these cases?
Who told you to collect them?
Well, who else
but the Chief
and the Head of the Department...
They also told me
to tell you to stick
to what you're ordered to do here.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yeah?
Place the suspect, Baekgoo,
under emergency arrest.
- Huh?
- The suspect...
No, the suspect dog.
Don't forget to read him his rights
at arrest
and no kibble until he confesses.
No chew sticks
or bones, either.
Only give him water, alright?
You may go.
I gave her all the trivial cases we had.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR OH JAE-PIL
Of course not.
She can't have it easy in exile.
PROSECUTOR KIM JIN-A
VICTIM STATEMENT FROM KIM MAL-SUN
17 HEADS OF CABBAGE WERE STOLEN
WITH TRACES OF KNIFE MARKS
PROSECUTOR KIM JIN-A
Hey, Mr. Kim.
You know the case of cabbage theft?
I've done some research,
and it's a really big deal.
We'll need to ask phone service providers
for location tracking.
- That's hilarious.
- I know.
How are things there?
Life is really nothing much, huh?
Every day feels like vacation here.
Sorry for interrupting your vacation.
Enjoy your time, then.
No, wait!
Did you have something to say?
Yeah, I did
but you sound too happy.
I don't want to interrupt your peace.
Since when were you so considerate?
What is it?
The prosecution will form a special team
for Gwang-to's case.
The team isn't to prosecute him, really.
I can't wait to see
what pathetic prosecutors join the team!
Don't say that
and be good when they call you, okay?
Also, call me
as soon as you're back in Seoul.
This is so boring.
Hello!
There's less than a 10% chance
that he'll wake up.
Your case of wrongful death suit
is looking likely
to rule in favor of the victim.
Sorry?
And you were on trial
for illegal prescription of narcotics
at the time.
What would you like me to do?
This patient has no family.
He wouldn't want to be
in a vegetative state
with just a 10% chance of waking up.
Breaking news.
New People's Future Party held
an emergency general meeting today
and decided to introduce
the S Group Special Counsel Act.
Sure.
The opposition needs to do its job, too.
This is to re-investigate
the allegations of political lobbying...
Call a meeting at Suojae tonight.
We're in full power
until Mr. President is released.
Yes, sir.
HERE'S THE REQUESTED INFORMATION
DAY TWO OF HUNGER STRIKE
UNTIL MR. PARK GWANG-TO IS INVESTIGATED
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY MUST SHOW JUSTICE
PASS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ACT
FOR PARK GWANG-TO!
DAY TWO OF HUNGER STRIKE
Is this hunger strike to fight
or to whine?
I hear it's healthy to starve a few days.
Let's go.
What the hell?
Should I have just shaved my head instead?
Perfect timing.
Did you do this?
FORMER PRESIDENT PARK PURCHASED LAND
UNDER HIS CLEANING LADY'S NAME
I have to be on my game, you know?
Impressive.
So, he acted like everyone's grandfather
only to be all about bribes?
He used his maid's name
to buy land in the green belt.
He'll definitely get
a special investigation.
The attack dog in the opposition
is just attacking Mr. Park
for the upcoming election.
Don't be fooled by the lie.
If he avoids the investigation,
he's guilty.
The special investigation is an excuse
to bully the former President.
Enjoy your special investigation!
This...
What is Sin-jin doing?
What's taking him so long?
Damn it.
IF HE AVOIDS THE INVESTIGATION,
HE'S GUILTY
HE USED HIS MAID'S NAME
TO BUY LAND IN THE GREEN BELT
PRESIDING JUDGE LEE HAN-YOUNG
MR. KWAK SANG-CHEOL
There's no way
I'm starving over three days.
Just one more day, until tomorrow.
The tree that Gwang-to is hanging onto
is shaking.
Gwang-to will strangle Sin-jin to survive
and Sin-jin will see this as a chance.
MR. KWAK CONTINUES THE HUNGER STRIKE
FOR A SPECIAL COUNSEL ACT
DAY TWO OF HUNGER STRIKE
Who do you think will be first
to stand by me
once the Special Counsel Act is passed?
I want you to be first.
The prosecution is preparing
a special investigation team.
There will be no point
in passing the bill, then.
People are now also talking
about the land purchases in green belt.
But once that case reaches the court
they'll just stall time
until it's forgotten.
I've been thinking about you a lot lately.
The more I think about it,
the more I realize I know about you.
Aren't you curious about how much I know?
I'm always thinking about you, too.
We'll get you back in Suojae
as soon as possible.
Sure, looking forward to it.
DOCTOR CHO JI-YUN
Please update me every two hours...
Dr. Cho?
We'll just get rid of him
if he causes trouble.
Police officers will be stationed
to guard Mr. Kwak's room from now on.
- I see.
- Where is he staying?
Sin-jin wouldn't just let Sun-won be.
He's in danger.
Please come this way.
Oh, my stomach!
Oh, no!
My stomach!
- Sir, are you okay?
- It hurts so much!
- Please help.
- It hurts!
My stomach hurts so much!
Oh, gosh.
I'm in so much pain!
Hey, I think I might have a gift
for acting.
Sin-jin will kill Sun-won.
What? Why would he kill his underling?
Because from the moment he's arrested,
he'll be Sin-jin's weakness.
The doctor in charge is in trial
for a case of medical fatality
and she's likely to be found guilty.
Sin-jin will try to use that
and bribe her.
This is ridiculous.
PROSECUTOR PARK CHEOL-WOO
FROM CHUNGNAM DISTRICT COURT
When did you wash your feet?
- They stink.
- Sorry.
Are you here?
Sometimes, patients in a coma
experience unexpected cardiac arrests.
I want him gone by morning.
Will I not be found guilty, then?
You'll be found innocent, as promised.
Okay, I'll keep you updated.
CHLORIDE
DR. CHO JI-YUN
Are you done?
The court orders
a reversal of the lower court's judgment.
The Defendant is found not guilty.
There seems to have been a problem
at the hospital.
Sorry?
I'll check.
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
Doctor!
What's wrong?
Please check him.
Let's see.
Hey, I have to go.
Hey!
Hey.
Sun-won ran off.
Look at you!
What happened?
I asked Sin-jin to get you
in the special investigation team.
Why?
Prosecute Gwang-to.
That's not what the team is for.
It's to help him!
That's just what Sin-jin is saying
to the Suojae people.
Sin-jin's real goal is
to get Gwang-to arrested
and become Suojae's boss.
So, you want me to help Sin-jin
achieve his goal?
We'll get rid of Gwang-to, then Sin-jin.
Don't think about anything else.
Fine.
What else should I know?
Sun-won just escaped
from the hospital.
What?
By the way
you visited Mr. President, right?
How is he doing?
How's his health?
It's crucial
that Suojae stays strong through this.
Mr. President is well.
But he's worried
about the special counsel.
The special investigation team is
ready to go.
I checked
the list of people on the team.
Mr. President will be released tomorrow
through the detention legality review.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes, that's a huge relief.
The opposition is pushing
for special hearing for S Group
and a special counsel, right?
We'll do our best
but stopping both would be...
They want a special counsel
for everything!
It's not like those members are
completely clean, either!
There's not a single soul
who hasn't taken my money
in Seocho-gu or Yeouido!
Let the special hearing take place.
What?
Take the special hearing,
and stop the special counsel.
I'll do my best.
You think
holding a special hearing is easy?
But it only lasts for a day.
Half of those on the hearing committee
will have taken money from you, anyway.
Just get through half a day of it.
- I'm worried about this.
- It'll be fine.
I'm sure it'll work out.
Do you think the guys at Suojae
want Mr. President to return?
I'm not sure.
Not everyone seemed like it.
I thought so, too.
Disgusting scumbags.
What?
Okay.
Mr. Kang
Sun-won escaped from the hospital.
What if he realizes
that we tried to kill him?
Do you know how they train elephants
at safaris?
From the moment these elephants are born
they're beaten with iron hooks
and taser batons.
Just like that,
the elephants lose their free will
and become slaves to the safari.
Until they die.
We will now begin
the detention hearing,
as requested by the Defendant.
You seem to be very worried
about Mr. President.
The review of the legality of detention
for Mr. Park
at the Seoul Central District Court
has been going on for eight hours.
Mr. Park is under arrest
for illicit political fund collection
and using borrowed names for purchases
but he has requested to be freed,
claiming an unfair detention.
Mr. Park claims
the arrest was politically motivated...
Do we have time to drop by Seonhwagak?
Yes.
Let's get a cake.
Oh, I see.
Now that I think about it,
it's the owner's birthday today.
SEONHWAGAK
HERE'S THE REQUESTED INFORMATION
Mr. Kang.
I'll go first.
What a relief.
How are you recovering?
Mr. Kang was very worried about you.
Let's sort out any misunderstandings
and just...
Mr. Kang?
I'll always have your back.
You should go home.
Sun-won.
Are you going to stab me, too
and be on the run for life?
I didn't think you'd ever wake up.
You weren't alive, nor dead.
You were bedridden and rotting.
Yet, people would've criticized you
for being a murderer.
Do you feel betrayed?
If so, stab me.
To cause me the same pain you feel
about being betrayed.
Go ahead.
Come on.
So, from now on
only kill those who I tell you to.
You'll never have to be in court, then.
I'm
sorry.
I have a job for you.
Good work.
I told you
I'd bring you back here
as soon as possible.
Alright.
Congratulations
on your safe return.
Thank you.
Do you still feel the same
about serving the nation?
Of course.
Amazing.
Cheers.
I'm a bit tired.
Let's call it a night.
The detention center is uncomfortable
whatever you do.
Go ahead. Keep drinking.
You know very well
that the press is getting out of control
and that Mr. President knows
all our weaknesses.
So, if anything bad happens
to Mr. President...
So
you want me to twist his neck?
No.
I'm sure
that Mr. President also knows
your weakness.
Doesn't that make you anxious?
The prosecution can finish him.
Sorry?
Congratulations
Mr. Kang!
Please
take good care of Suojae.
We'll do our best
to serve you well.
Oh, come here, Mr. Lee.
Good work, everyone.
Sin-jin's rebellion
has begun.
Do you think
he might've shot himself to death?
But
how can someone committing suicide
shoot himself twice?
Bang.
Bang!
Nam-yong came to me
and told me something.
He told me
never to trust the young judge
Sin-jin may bring.
And so
I never trusted you from the start.
Did Sin-jin send you?
No.
Yeah, I bet everyone in there
wants my head chopped off.
How can they ever be at peace
when I know their weaknesses, right?
But aren't you the same?
- What?
- Didn't Nam-yong tell you?
That he gave Sin-jin
all your weaknesses?
What are you talking about?
The record of illicit political funds
of assemblymen
and the past and present Presidents
that Nam-yong collected
in the National Election Commission.
Of course, you're in it, too.
Nam-yong...
That bastard!
You don't have anywhere to run
as long as Sin-jin has that file on you.
Why don't you just do your best
with what you have now?
Like getting revenge, for example.
Join me
and I'll turn prison into Suojae for you.
There, you can form
a new government with new people
and make development plans.
You won't be bored.
He's a prosecutor
on your special investigation team.
Sure, whatever it is
let's start tomorrow.
But you know what?
I'm too tired tonight.
Aren't you coming?
No.
You always get your job done.
Mr. President
has disappeared.
Damn it.
He probably knows
what we've been doing by now.
"We"?
The one who hired a guy
to try to kill Mr. President is
Mr. Kang, not us.
You think Mr. President will believe that?
No.
We shouldn't be here right now.
Shouldn't we find a solution?
- Right?
- Yeah.
Mr. Kang.
You caused all of this
so take responsibility for everything
and leave.
Grab him.
Grab him!
Is having a junkie for a daughter
and a cheating wife not enough?
What?
Shut it right now.
This is defamation
through false information
you bastard!
What are you doing? Grab him!
Grab him!
Grab him from that side.
Arrest him!
Arrest him right now!
Come on. Arrest him immediately!
Get rid of him right now!
You think you can get them on board
by talking to them like this?
And
you don't think
I have something on you, too?
Should I start with that clip of you
sexually assaulting your assistant?
You evil bastard.
Die!
You fucking bastard!
Oh, gosh.
Mr. Kang.
Hurry!
Why?
Why now?
Please...
help.
Yeah.
We
just protected justice.
I won't forget you.
SUOJAE
What took you so long?
What happened?
I told you
the day I became the head of Suojae
I'd let you sit beside me.
But why...
HERE'S THE REQUESTED INFORMATION
Wow.
The photos look great.
Were you also the one who saved Tae-seong?
I told you I'd stop Nam-yong
from becoming the Chief Justice.
You did.
And Yong-jin?
The victim
wanted Yong-jin to be tried in court.
So, you also stole the three billion won.
You were so obvious with these attacks.
How did I not even notice the pain?
So, you approached me
for me.
The evil
can never protect justice.
If you took over the Judiciary
and even Suojae
Korea would suffer
from your narrow-mindedness
and wickedness that you'd call "justice".
At the top of the Judiciary
as the head of Suojae
I could change everything.
I could stop the rich from getting away
with suspended sentences
and stop powerful people
from determining guilt and innocence.
If you still want justice,
you still have time.
Join me.
Your definition of justice is
just for you.
It's unjust and narrow-minded
for the sake of authority.
No.
I never abuse my authority for myself.
You don't deserve to say that.
Look what you've done.
You're nothing
but a power-driven, cruel murderer
who always takes bribes for trials.
This is justice putting people to trial.
What about the lives you sacrificed?
Can you say the same to those people?
They were just sacrifices for justice.
Don't you get it?
I thought you'd understand me.
But
if that's not the case
I have to do it for justice.
Why did I think you were like me?
My trivial guilt
for imprisoning your father ruined me.
And that was your choice.
If you don't stop here
the future Sin-jin will be even more evil.
This was your last chance.
LEE HAN-YOUNG
- Hey!
- What's wrong?
- Fine!
- What?
- Why?
- Get out, you brats.
What's going on?
SEOK JEONG-HO
Hey.
I told you not to come to our class.
Why do you keep coming to our class
and kicking my kids out?
Go back to your class.
- Go back!
- Sir!
Do you have a best friend?
What in the world are you talking about?
No, I don't. Why?
To me
this guy, Han-young, is my best friend.
Do you want a cake for that or what?
No, I just...
My friend, Han-young,
has to become a judge.
So, I'll do whatever it takes
to help Han-young
enjoy the best environment for studying!
Hey.
I knew you said you'd study for real
but are you set on becoming a judge now?
Yes.
Look at you!
Why do you want to become a judge?
To restore justice or something?
He will!
Get his revenge!
What?
Both of you, come with me.
- Wait!
- Follow me!
My ear really hurts!
Gosh, this is heavy.
One, two!
Stop it.
Han-young
you have to become a judge, alright?
You got us kicked out
when I was trying to study!
My friend is Judge Lee Han-young!
He's incredible!
Keep it down! You're so embarrassing!
Hey, give it to me.
Why are you even complaining?
It's so light.
Man, I'm so tired.
- Jeong-ho.
- Yeah?
- You know it, right?
- What?
That I can run faster than you can!
Hey, this is cheating!
Come here!
The presidential election is tomorrow.
The early voting turnout is at 32.45%
and the candidates
from the ruling and opposition
are doing their last sprints
in Yeouido and at the city hall.
Sir.
Are you okay, sir?
Are you okay?
Hold on. I'll get the doctor.
The scar was very deep.
Thankfully, it only reached
your jugular vein.
Had the weapon reached your carotid artery
at the slightest
you couldn't have lasted a minute
from the bleeding.
Mr. Kim Yun-cheol was elected
by winning 49.8% of the votes
in the final tally of votes.
Maybe the world will actually change now.
Anyway, we have to keep you here
for a week
and see how you do.
Just sanitize his wound
and dress it today.
See you.
Just in case you get the wrong message
I'm just dropping by
while visiting another friend.
I just had some time.
I thought you were really going to die.
People die once, not twice.
And have you already died once?
You say it like you have.
You're right.
Code Blue.
- Cardiac arrest patient in Room 507.
- Oh, no.
Nurses and doctors,
please see the patient.
I can do the rest. You can go.
You just need to tape it. Sorry.
Cardiac arrest patient in Room 507.
Nurses and doctors,
please see the patient.
Code Blue.
Cardiac arrest patient in Room 507.
Can you help me?
I'm fine. Smile.
I'm sorry.
For slapping your face
the first time we met.
I don't think
I've apologized for that yet.
Did you throw away the old gauze
we took off?
It has to go in the biohazard bin.
No.
Oh, did I clean it?
I've been so busy.
I'll get going, then.
Sorry.
Se-hee...
What are you doing?
Damn it.
Hey, get out!
Mr. Woo Gyo-hun and Mr. Gwak Sun-won,
Sin-jin's assassin
died in Suojae last night.
I heard Sin-jin killed Gyo-hun.
But Jin-han is also dead.
They say a robber killed him,
but I'm not convinced.
All videos from the surrounding cameras
were deleted.
Whatever it was, it wasn't a robber.
I know.
Are you okay, by the way?
Physically, yes.
But
I think I'm getting accused.
What?
Sin-jin seems to have accused me.
You should turn yourself in for now.
I'll take care of the rest.
No.
This is something I have to do.
What?
Okay, then.
Han-young ran away.
Are you sure you should be out and about?
Why? Are you worried?
That you'd be in danger
once I get arrested?
Come on. Of course not.
I believe in your good character.
Do you trust people?
No.
I trust money and power.
Oh.
Of course.
I have to meet Gwang-to.
Request an attorney visitation.
Sorry?
Mr. Kang Sin-jin,
the Chief Judge of the Seoul Central Court
has been named as the suspect
behind the death of Mr. Woo Gyo-hun
at Mr. Park Gwang-to's home in Gyeonggi-do
two days ago.
But the investigation discovered
that there was an accomplice
present on-site with Sin-jin.
Mr. Kang has helped our attorneys win
quite a lot of cases in court.
If the world hears about that
our firm will crumble to the ground
and your brother and I will be arrested.
Dad...
So, we'll have to give
what Sin-jin wants.
He killed a man!
So what?
You think he won't snitch on us
just because he's murdered someone?
Se-hee
don't tell me you've fallen for Han-young.
Pass me the food.
- You got everything ready?
- Yes.
Good work.
Come in.
This is a class on real estate investment
in Seoul.
What?
They give lectures on frauds...
Get out!
I've come all the way to Hyenam,
and you treat me like I'm invisible
without a single colleague to eat with.
But he has a drinking buddy
after pulling a housing scam on dozens
and assaulting people.
You got it all wrong.
I'm investigating him.
Is this how you do it?
Huh?
Well...
You'll learn in time.
Bullshit.
What?
What did you just say?
You have an imported car
of over 100 million won.
That's from Mr. Hwang,
the CEO of Hyenam Jeil Trading, right?
You're out of line.
That studio unit in the city is
under your son's name.
How did a college student afford that?
You trying to end your career?
Remember, you're in exile.
Just live like you're dead, alright?
Sir
you know why I've been exiled, right?
So many people called me a crazy bitch
when I was going after Mr. Jang Tae-sik.
Well, I get how you get the job done now.
You want to see
how the crazy bitch from Seoul does it?
Hand your friend over to me.
Breaking news.
The new suspect
in Mr. Woo's murder
at Mr. Park Gwang-to's house
has been confirmed.
A DNA analysis of the blood left
at the scene
- pointed to Lee Han-young
- What?
the judge
at the Seoul Central District Court.
The prosecution held
an emergency briefing session
to confirm the formal indictment of Lee
as an accomplice in Woo's murder case
this afternoon.
I don't know where to go.
So, Mr. Kang was just a regular?
I had no idea that he was a Chief Judge.
But...
how did the guy...
Exactly. You never know
what people are thinking.
When was his most recent visit?
I can't remember.
I'm not at the restaurant all day.
Find me before the police does.
That's the least you can do
to be cleared of the accusation.
It won't take long.
I was ready to go all the way
when I started, anyway.
I'm still alive.
THE JUDGE RETURNS
Where is justice in Korea?
Sin-jin really might return at this rate.
I wonder if he still has
more cards to play.
At the end of the day,
only money and power persevere.
Korea's judicial system has
completely fallen.
Don't worry. The tables will turn again.
Don't let things get worse.
Turn yourself in.
We need new justice to change the world.
I'll prove
that the justice I've chosen is right.
Han-young!
I'll return to the court.
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim